{
    "questions":[
        {
            "id": 0,
            "question": "How long have snakes been roaming the Earth?",
            "a":"3 million years",
            "b":"30 million years",
            "c":"130 million years",
            "d":"200 million years",
            "answerkey":"c"
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "What characteristics do all snakes share?",
            "a":"They are carnivoes",
            "b":"They are all programming languages",
            "c":"Cold-blooded",
            "d":"They are both carnivores and cold-blooded",
            "answerkey":"c"
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "How snakes hear?",
            "a":"With small ears",
            "b":"Through their skin",
            "c":"Through their tail",
            "d":"They don't use their ears at all",
            "answerkey":"b"
        },
        {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "What don't snakes see?",
            "a":"Colour",
            "b":"Light",
            "c":"Both of the above",
            "d":"Other snakes",
            "answerkey":"a"
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "What unique vision ability do boas and pythons possess?",
            "a":"Night vision",
            "b":"Infared vision",
            "c":"See through walls",
            "d":"They don't have vision",
            "answerkey":"b"
        },
        {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "How does a snake smell?",
            "a":"Through its nose",
            "b":"Through its tongue",
            "c":"Through its ears",
            "d":"Both through its nose and its tongues",
            "answerkey":"d"
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "Where are Jacobson's organs located in snakes?",
            "a":"Mouth",
            "b":"Tail",
            "c":"Stomach",
            "d":"Liver",
            "answerkey":"a"
        },
        {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "Snakes have very similar internal organs compared to humans. Snakes, however; lack the following:",
            "a":"A diaphragm",
            "b":"Intestines",
            "c":"Lungs",
            "d":"Kidney",
            "answerkey":"a"
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "Snakes have different shaped lungs than humans. What do snakes have?",
            "a":"An elongated right lung",
            "b":"A small left lung",
            "c":"Both of the above",
            "d":"None of the above",
            "answerkey":"c"
        },
        {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "What's true about two-headed snakes?",
            "a":"They're a myth!",
            "b":"Rarely survive in the wild",
            "c":"They're very dangerous",
            "d":"They can kiss each other",
            "answerkey":"b"
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "What substance covers a snake's skin?",
            "a":"Calcium",
            "b":"Keratin",
            "c":"Copper",
            "d":"Iron",
            "answerkey":"b"
        }
    ]

} 